W. R. "Bob" Poage Personal papers, Inclusive: 1766-2008, undated, Bulk: 1937-1978
Baylor University Libraries
- Photographs, 1861-1991, undated; 3
  - W. R. Poage Retirement Announcement at Waco, Texas Home (06-03), 1977 September (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - 1964 Africa Trip (07-01) (1 of 4) (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - 1964 Africa Trip (07-01) (2 of 4) (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - 1964 Africa Trip (07-01) (3 of 4) (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - 1964 Africa Trip (07-01) (4 of 4) (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - 1970 Africa Trip (07-01) (1 of 8) (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - 1970 Africa Trip (07-01) (2 of 8) (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - 1970 Africa Trip (07-01) (3 of 8) (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - 1970 Africa Trip (07-01) (4 of 8) (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - 1970 Africa Trip (07-01) (5 of 8) (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - 1970 Africa Trip (07-01) (6 of 8) (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - 1970 Africa Trip (07-01) (7 of 8) (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - 1970 Africa Trip (07-01) (8 of 8) (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - 1972 Africa Trip (07-01), 1972 May (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - General Africa Photos (07-01), 1972, undated (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - W. R. Poage with Agriculture Committee (08-01) (1 of 3), 1969-1979, undated (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - W. R. Poage with Agriculture Committee (08-01) (2 of 3), 1969-1979, undated (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - W. R. Poage with Agriculture Committee (08-01) (3 of 3), 1969-1979, undated (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - W. R. Poage with Astronauts and NASA Representatives (09-01), undated (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - W. R. Poage with Colleagues, Constituents, and Delegates (10-01) (1 of 9), 1966-1977, undated (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - W. R. Poage with Colleagues, Constituents, and Delegates (10-01) (2 of 9), 1966-1977, undated (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - W. R. Poage with Colleagues, Constituents, and Delegates (10-01) (3 of 9), 1966-1977, undated (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - W. R. Poage with Colleagues, Constituents, and Delegates (10-01) (4 of 9), 1966-1977, undated (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - W. R. Poage with Colleagues, Constituents, and Delegates (10-01) (5 of 9), 1966-1977, undated (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - W. R. Poage with Colleagues, Constituents, and Delegates (10-01) (6 of 9), 1966-1977, undated (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - W. R. Poage with Colleagues, Constituents, and Delegates (10-01) (7 of 9), 1966-1977, undated (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - W. R. Poage with Colleagues, Constituents, and Delegates (10-01) (8 of 9), 1966-1977, undated (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - W. R. Poage with Colleagues, Constituents, and Delegates (10-01) (9 of 9), 1966-1977, undated (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - W. R. Poage and Others at Boots and Saddle Club (11-01), 1965 February 17 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Trips to Central and South America (12-01) (1 of 7), 1966-1973, undated (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Trips to Central and South America (12-01) (2 of 7), 1966-1973, undated (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Trips to Central and South America (12-01) (3 of 7), 1966-1973, undated (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Trips to Central and South America (12-01) (4 of 7), 1966-1973, undated (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Trips to Central and South America (12-01) (5 of 7), 1966-1973, undated (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Trips to Central and South America (12-01) (6 of 7), 1966-1973, undated (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Trips to Central and South America (12-01) (7 of 7), 1966-1973, undated (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Dinosaurs (13-01), undated (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - W. R. Poage at Campaign Events (14-01), 1972, undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Trip to Guyana (15-01) (1 of 3), 1966 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Trip to Guyana (15-01) (2 of 3), 1966 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Trip to Guyana (15-01) (3 of 3), 1966 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Trip to Argentina (15-02), 1969 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - South America (15-03), 1968 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - South America (15-04) (1 of 4), 1964 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - South America (15-04) (2 of 4), 1964 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - South America (15-04) (3 of 4), 1964 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - South America (15-04) (4 of 4), 1964 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - McKinney, Texas (16-01), 1946-1952, undated (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Maid of Cotton Events (16-02) (1 of 2), circa 1977 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Maid of Cotton Events (16-02) (2 of 2), circa 1977 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - W. R. Poage with Boy Scouts in Washington, D. C. (16-03), undated (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - W. R. Poage with 4-H'ers and Tasting Strawberries (16-04), undated (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Bob Poage Day, Temple, Texas (16-05), undated (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - W. R. Poage in Killeen, Texas (16-06), 1974-1975, undated (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - W. R. Poage at Chicago Mercantile Exchange (16-07), 1973 November 9 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Photos Around Texas (16-08), 1978, undated (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - W. R. Poage at Assorted Events (16-09), 1963-1978, undated (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - W. R. Poage at Luncheons and Dining Events (16-10), 1963-1977, undated (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - W. R. Poage at Receptions (16-11), 1963-1978 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Beirut, Lebanon (17-01), undated (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Iran (17-02) (1 of 3), undated (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Iran (17-02) (2 of 3), undated (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Iran (17-02) (3 of 3), undated (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Yemen (17-03), undated (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - W. R. Poage in India (17-04) (1 of 2), 1972, undated (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - W. R. Poage in India (17-04) (2 of 2), 1972, undated (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - W. R. Poage in India (17-05) (1 of 2), undated (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - W. R. Poage in India (17-05) (2 of 2), undated (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Yemen Consultative Assembly (17-06), 1972 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - W. R. Poage in Africa (17-07), undated (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - W. R. Poage and Others on Far East Tour (18-01), undated (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Taipei, Taiwan (18-02), 1968 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Japan (18-03) (1 of 4), circa 1968 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Japan (18-03) (2 of 4), circa 1968 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Japan (18-03) (3 of 4), circa 1968 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Japan (18-03) (4 of 4), circa 1968 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Korea (18-04) (1 of 4), 1969 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Korea (18-04) (2 of 4), 1969 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Korea (18-04) (3 of 4), 1969 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Korea (18-04) (4 of 4), 1969 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Korea (18-05 and 18-06), 1971 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Spain Photos Printed as Postcards (19-01) (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Spain Photos Printed as Postcards (19-01) (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Dedication of Screwworm Eradication Facility, Tuxtia Gutierrez, Chiapas, Mexico (19-02) (1 of 2), 1976 August 25 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Dedication of Screwworm Eradication Facility, Tuxtia Gutierrez, Chiapas, Mexico (19-02) (2 of 2), 1976 August 25 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Europe (19-03), 1963 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Interparliamentary Union in Tehran, Iran (19-04), 1966 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Interparliamentary Union in Vienna, Austria (19-05), 1969 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - W. R. Poage in Office, at Events, and with Committee on Agriculture (20-01) (1 of 3), undated (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - W. R. Poage in Office, at Events, and with Committee on Agriculture (20-01) (2 of 3), undated (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - W. R. Poage in Office, at Events, and with Committee on Agriculture (20-01) (3 of 3), undated (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Secretary Freeman’s Research Study Trip to Peoria, Illinois, New Orleans, Louisiana, and Mission, Texas (20-02), 1965 May 27-29 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Reception for Japanese Minister of Agriculture, Hosted by U.S. Department of Agriculture (20-03) (1 of 2), 1973 October 5 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Reception for Japanese Minister of Agriculture, Hosted by U.S. Department of Agriculture (20-03) (2 of 2), 1973 October 5 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Assorted Photos from Events (21-01) (1 of 2), 1973-1979, undated (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Assorted Photos from Events (21-01) (2 of 2), 1973-1979, undated (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Credit Reception (21-01), 1978 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - House Gymnasium Dinner (21-01), 1978 July 12 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Lew Barringer Dinner (21-01), 1976 April 7 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Liberal Pancake Day (21-01), 1973 March 6 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - National Limestone Institute Conventions (21-01), 1963-1974 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Rural Electrification Administration Breakfast (21-01), 1974 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Reception at Rayburn Building, Washington, D.C. (21-01), 1975 October 22 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Reception for John Chettle of the South Africa Foundation (21-01), 1975 July 23 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Reception for O.C. Fisher’s Book “Cactus Jack” (21-01), 1978 July 26 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Reception Honoring Retiring Agriculture Committee Members (21-01), 1978 October 12 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Sheraton Peabody in Memphis, Tennessee (21-01), undated (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Sunflower Reception for Bob Bergland (21-01), 1977 March (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Texas Co-Op Power Photos (21-01), undated (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Texas Congressional Delegation Luncheon (21-01), 1975 September 17 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Texas Hospital Association Meeting (21-01), circa 1973 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Texas-Style Reception (21-01), 1978 July 11 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - W. R. Poage and Frances C. Poage at a Reception in Vienna, Austria (21-01), undated (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - W. R. Poage at Rally for J. J. Pickle (21-01), undated (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - W. R. Poage Receiving National Association of Conservation Districts Award (21-01), undated (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - W. R. Poage Speaking at Reception (21-01), undated (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - W. R. Poage with Ed B. Snead (21-01), undated (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - W. R. Poage with Other Politicians in Tuxedos (21-01), undated (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - Portrait Presentation of W. R. Poage (22-01) (1 of 2), 1968 February 26 (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - Portrait Presentation of W. R. Poage (22-01) (2 of 2), 1968 February 26 (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - W. R. Poage with Constituents, Colleagues, and Politicians (22-02), 1964-1972, undated (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - W. R. Poage with Visitors to his Washington, D.C. Office (23-01), 1975, undated (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - W. R. Poage Receiving Honorary Degree from Mary-Hardin Baylor (23-02), 1973 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - American Institute for Character Education Luncheon (23-03), 1971 November 17 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - General Event Photographs (23-03), undated (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Milk Producer’s Institute Event in Arlington, Texas (23-03), 1970 July (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Reception in Canberra, Australia for Interparliamentary Union (23-03), 1966 April 13 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - W. R. Poage Receiving Westinghouse Phone (23-03), 1979 July-August (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - W. R. Poage Speaking at Dinner (23-03), undated (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - W. R. Poage with Olin Teague, O. Wolfsenberger, E. T. S. Pearce (23-03), undated (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - W. R. Poage with Richard L. Epperson (23-03), 1978 January 30 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Dedication of W. R. Poage Federal Building, Temple, Texas (24-01), 1976 October 13 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Local Speaking Engagement (24-01), undated (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Temple, Texas Grassland Forage Center Groundbreaking (24-01), 1961 November 6 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Temple, Texas Library Ribbon Cutting (24-01), undated (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Temple, Texas Veterans Administration Groundbreaking (24-01 and 25-01), 1964 November 11 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Temple, Texas Veteran’s Administration Hospital Ceremony (24-01) (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Temple, Texas Veteran’s Administration Hospital Ceremony (24-01) (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - W. R. Poage and Helen C. Poage at Coast Guard Helicopter Showcase (24-01), 1948 April 8 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - W. R. Poage at Local Events (24-01), undated (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - W. R. Poage Giving the Keys of a New Clifton, Texas Home to the New Homeowners (24-01), undated (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Dedication of W. R. Poage Legislative Library Center (24-02), 1979 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - W. R. Poage in Troy, Texas (24-02), undated (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - W. R. Poage with Delegates from Bahama Islands, Texas State Technical Institute Representatives (24-03), 1973 February 26 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - General Speaking Events (25-01), undated (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Majorca, Spain (25-01), 1967 March (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Autographed Photo of Lyndon B. Johnson (25-02), 1942 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - W. R. and Frances C. Poage with Jimmy and Rosalynn Carter (25-02), undated (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Polaroids of Rural Home and Property (25-03), undated (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - House Agriculture Committee in Tunis (25-04), 1964 November 18 (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Unidentified Men with a Tabby Cat (25-05), undated (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - House Agriculture Committee in Kansas and Missouri (26-01), undated (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Baylor Exes Meeting (26-02), 1966 June 26 (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - Event Photos (26-02) (1 of 2), 1966-1975, undated (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - Event Photos (26-02) (2 of 2), 1966-1975, undated (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - W. R. Poage and Others at Reception (26-02), undated (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - W. R. Poage and Nelda Lee Pool of Odessa, Texas (26-02), 1977 January 20 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - W. R. Poage at Events with Colleagues and Constituents (26-03) (1 of 5), 1953-1978, undated (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - W. R. Poage at Events, with Colleagues and Constituents (26-03) (2 of 5), 1953-1978, undated (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - W. R. Poage at Events, with Colleagues and Constituents (26-03) (3 of 5), 1953-1978, undated (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - W. R. Poage at Events, with Colleagues and Constituents (26-03) (4 of 5), 1953-1978, undated (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - W. R. Poage at Events, with Colleagues and Constituents (26-03) (5 of 5), 1953-1978, undated (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - W. R. Poage on his Throckmorton County, Texas Farm (26-03), undated (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - W. R. Poage in His Office (26-04), undated (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Image of Pigs (26-05), undated (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Fort Worth, Texas Botanical Gardens (27-01), undated (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Far East Trip (27-02) (1 of 2), undated (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Far East Trip (27-02) (2 of 2), undated (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - India Trip (27-03) (1 of 3), undated (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - India Trip (27-03) (2 of 3), undated (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - India Trip (27-03) (3 of 3), undated (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Bob Poage Day at W. R. Poage Land Technology Center (27-04) (1 of 2), 1970 December 7 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Bob Poage Day at W. R. Poage Land Technology Center (27-04) (2 of 2), 1970 December 7 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Groundbreaking Ceremony for W. R. Poage Legislative Library Center (28-01), undated (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Aerial Images by the “Fighting 84”, undated (Box 125 OVZ, Folder 27)
  - Aerial Photo of Sugar House, 1973 (Box 153 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Aerial Photo of Waco, Texas, undated (Box 153 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Aerial Photo of Worksite, undated (Box 153 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - “After Work,” Van Sorlau, undated (Box 153 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Agriculture Committee at Military Demonstration, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Agriculture Committee Photos, circa 1970 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Air Force C-82 Packet Plane, undated (Box 153 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Air Force One, undated (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Animal Photographs, Birds, undated (Box 153 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Animal Photographs, CN-659, Brown Cows Grazing, undated (Box 153 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Animal Photographs, CN-1448, Sheep Shearing, undated (Box 153 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - Animal Photographs, CN02623, Meadows Lea Station, Canterbury, undated (Box 153 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - Animal Photographs, CN-2686, Cecil Peak Station, Southland, undated (Box 153 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - Animal Photographs, Cows, undated (Box 153 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - Animal Photographs, USAS 1009, Penguin at Red Rock Ridge, undated (Box 153 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - Animal Photographs, USAS 4235, Departing Bay of Whales, undated (Box 153 OVZ, Folder 13)
  - Animal Photographs, USAS 5692, Skiing Penguins, undated (Box 153 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - Animal Photographs, USAS 5694, Emperor Penguins Courtship, undated (Box 153 OVZ, Folder 15)
  - Animal Photographs, USAS 5695, Emperor Penguins, undated (Box 153 OVZ, Folder 16)
  - Animal Photographs, USAS 5699, Emperor Penguins Conference, undated (Box 153 OVZ, Folder 17)
  - Animal Photographs, USAS 5795, Three Adelie Penguins, undated (Box 153 OVZ, Folder 18)
  - Atomic Blast, undated (Box 154 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Autographed Photo of W. R. Poage, Harry Johnson, and three others, 1951 (Box 125 OVZ, Folder 28)
  - Autographed Photo of W. R. Poage with Rosalynn Carter, undated (Box 125 OVZ, Folder 29)
  - Baby Photos of Randy Freeman, circa 1954 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - Bangladesh Trip, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - “Bear Lake — Rockies,” P. A. Glick, undated (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Biblical Scene, Dixon Wector Baptismal, 1914 August 30 (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - Bicentennial Banner, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - “Black Eyed Pea Jamboree”, undated (Box 154 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - “Blue Northerner,” E. M. Schwietz, undated (Box 154 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Bob Bullock at Work, circa 1983 (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - Brazos Directors, circa 1946 (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - Calvert, Texas Home Dedication, 1967 (Box 54, Folder 31)
  - Chairman Mazzoli, 1985 May 23, undated (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Childhood Photo of W. R. Poage, undated (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - City of Waco by James Whitehead, undated (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Agriculture in San Angelo, Texas, 1953 June (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Congressional Delegation Departing Dallas, Texas for Pacific Theater, 1946 January 5 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Congressional Portraits with Index (1 of 7), undated (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Congressional Portraits with Index (2 of 7), undated (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Congressional Portraits with Index (3 of 7), undated (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Congressional Portraits with Index (4 of 7), undated (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Congressional Portraits with Index (5 of 7), undated (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Congressional Portraits with Index (6 of 7), undated (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Congressional Portraits with Index (7 of 7), undated (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Construction of 600 Edgewood, Waco (1 of 2), circa 1950 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Construction of 600 Edgewood, Waco (2 of 2), circa 1950 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Coryell County, Texas Courthouse, undated (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - “Cotton Harvest,” E. M. Schwietz, undated (Box 154 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - “Cotton Saturday,” E. M. Schwietz, undated (Box 154 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - “Cottonseed on the Hoof,” E. M. Schwietz, undated (Box 154 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Courthouses, undated (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - “Decline In Our Foreign Sales”, undated (Box 154 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Delegates in Front of Plane, undated (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Departing Andrews Air Force Base for Interparliamentary Union, 1962 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Drawing of Killeen Homestead, Bob Klingensmith, 1976 (Box 154 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - “Erinnerung an Die Schwiez” Lake in Switzerland, undated (Box 154 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - “Flowers,” T. L. Prevost, undated (Box 154 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - Framed Drawing of W. R. Poage, undated (Box 156 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Frances C. Poage, Congressional Club Annual Breakfast, 1954 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Frances C. Poage Headshot, circa 1968 March 15 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Frances C. Poage with Margaret Chase Smith and Others, undated (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - General Travel Photos, undated (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Gildersleeve Photo of a House in Waco, undated (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Group Photo with W. R. Poage and Colleagues, undated (Box 125 OVZ, Folder 31)
  - Group Photos from San Juan, 1955 January 15 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Harold D. Cooley Signing the Agriculture Act of 1965 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Hat and Shoes of W. R. Poage Outside of Ancient Mosque, Timbuktu, Mali, 1964 December 2 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Heilman Studio Portraits of Man and Woman, undated (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - Helen C. Poage Passport Photos, circa 1946 (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - “High Noon,” E. M. Schwietz, undated (Box 154 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - Home of Edith and Jim Byrne, 1942 (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - House Committee on Agriculture, undated (Box 154 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - House Committee on Agriculture, 1968 (Box 154 OVZ, Folder 13)
  - House Committee on Agriculture, 1972 (Box 154 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - House Committee on Agriculture, 1974 (Box 154 OVZ, Folder 15)
  - “How We Lived,” Images Used for Book, undated (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - “How We Lived,” Photos from Around Waco, circa 1983 (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - Image of Horse Statue, undated (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - Image of Killeen, Texas Train Station, undated (Box 154 OVZ, Folder 16)
  - Image of Office with Flowers and Portrait of W. R. Poage on Wall, undated (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - Image of Plaza Mayor de Guonajuato, undated (Box 154 OVZ, Folder 17)
  - Index of People Featured in Series (A-Z), undated (Box 124 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Interparliamentary Union, Brasilia, 1962 (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - Interparliamentary Union in Rome, Italy, Poage on Crutches, 1948 September-October (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - John Dowdy at his Desk, undated (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - Korea Trip (1 of 2), undated (Box 55, Folder 37)
  - Korea Trip (2 of 2), undated (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - “Lake Providence, Louisiana,” P. A. Glick, undated (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Marvin Leath, Jack Hightower, Herbert Reynolds, and Unnamed Person at Baylor University, circa 1983 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Lists of Poage Photographs, 1991, undated (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Lyndon B. Johnson Presenting W. R. Poage with Pen Used to Sign Legislation, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Lyndon B. Johnson, Signed Photographs, undated (Box 154 OVZ, Folder 18)
  - Man and Woman at Beach, 1984 June (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - “March in East Texas,” E. M. Schwietz, undated (Box 154 OVZ, Folder 19)
  - “McLennan County — Before 1980,” Archival Images Used in Book, undated (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - “McLennan County — Before 1980,” Local Images Used in Book, undated (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - “Middle Busting,” E. M. Schwietz, undated (Box 154 OVZ, Folder 20)
  - Miriam A. Ferguson, 1960 January 14 (Box 125 OVZ, Folder 32)
  - Mrs. H. E. Conger, undated (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - “My First 85 Years,” Chapters 1-4 Images, undated (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - “My First 85 Years,” Chapters 5-8 Images, undated (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - “My First 85 Years,” Chapters 9-12 Images, undated (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - “My First 85 Years,” Chapters 13-16 Images, undated (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - “My First 85 Years,” Chapters 17-20 Images, undated (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - “My First 85 Years,” Chapters 21-24 Images, undated (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - “My First 85 Years,” Chapters 25-28 Images, undated (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - “My First 85 Years,” Film Strips and Contact Sheets, undated (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - “My First 85 Years,” Unused Photos, undated (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - National Limestone Convention, Washington, D.C., 1960 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - National Rural Electric Cooperative Association Event in Chicago, Illinois, 1944 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Old Faithful Stamp, undated (Box 154 OVZ, Folder 21)
  - “Old Ironsides”, circa 1927 (Box 155 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Painted Landscape, C. M. Hennings, undated (Box 155 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Paraguay, Visit of House Agricultural Committee, 1955 November 14-15 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Passport Photos of Unknown Man and Woman, circa 1946 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Pat M. Neff, Campaign Poster, 1930 (Box 155 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Photo Album, Congressman Poage’s Visit to Pakistan, 1972 November 26-27 (Box 157 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Photo Album, Dedication of Veterans Administration Hospital, Temple, Texas, 1967 June 17 (Box 158 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Photo Album [Disassembled], Frances C. Poage (1 of 15), undated (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Photo Album [Disassembled], Frances C. Poage (2 of 15), undated (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Photo Album [Disassembled], Frances C. Poage (3 of 15), undated (Box 56, Folder 25)